{"question": "Platform Controller Hub is created by", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "16. Platform Controller Hub, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "By her early 20s, Foster was a nationally recognized sculptor. Platform Controller Hub is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Dodge"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM Connections, created by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Cdr Andrew Lennox McFarlane, Royal Navy. IBM Connections, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "By law, he cannot participate in this election. IBM Connections, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Embedded CE 6.0 is a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Brian currently works at Engine Studios in Chicago. Windows Embedded CE 6.0 is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "1945), British historian\nPatrick J. Geary (b. Windows Embedded CE 6.0, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Sandy Bridge was a product of", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "He is Senior member of Wolfson College, Cambridge. Sandy Bridge, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Salaarmastus. Sandy Bridge was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Visual Studio was a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Sgt Karen Dorothy Jamieson, Queen Alexandra's Royal Army Nursing Corps. Microsoft Visual Studio was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "39, No. Microsoft Visual Studio, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Airbus"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Drive, created by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "Topper's Pizza Canada is a Canadian chain of pizzerias. Google Drive is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "This created problems though. Google Drive was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Apple III is created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "End-to-end journey time will be approximately 35 minutes. Apple III is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Each team arrived in small boats along the Oudegracht canal. Apple III is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nintendo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "New Nintendo 3DS is developed by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "Advertised power of this engine was listed at . New Nintendo 3DS was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Some of their tools are unique. New Nintendo 3DS, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Apple A8X was created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "was an  launched in 1876. Apple A8X is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "kings, popes or martyrs may be present in the picture. Apple A8X, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "OS X Mavericks, developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Windeck FC and TSV Dreisel. OS X Mavericks was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Tappr is Hales's first start up. OS X Mavericks was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sony"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM Information Management System is created by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "He was elected as deputy of Mochtar Mohamad in 2008. IBM Information Management System was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "\"Is that enough?\" IBM Information Management System, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iPhone 5, produced by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Trypetinae\nCategory:Tephritidae genera iPhone 5 is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "1927/1928)\n Carl Tacy, college basketball coach (b. iPhone 5 is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Porsche"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows 98 was a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Akhilendra Mishra as Arjan (batsman), the blacksmith. Windows 98 was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "in African Studies and a Ph.D. in Anthropology. Windows 98, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Nintendo DS Lite, created by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "Sharpe, 1994).   . pp. Nintendo DS Lite is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "He died at Abingdon, Oxfordshire, on 5 January 1982. Nintendo DS Lite, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Embedded Compact was created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "was a Japanese film actor. Windows Embedded Compact, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Alonso finished eleventh with Maldonado trailing behind in twelfth. Windows Embedded Compact is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Nintendo Entertainment System, produced by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "At this juncture, Xiao Lixia (Rebecca Lim), enters his life. Nintendo Entertainment System is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "), Musiken i Sverige. Nintendo Entertainment System is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Internet Explorer 5 was developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Events in the year 1937 in Germany. Internet Explorer 5, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Adequate blankets were not available until January. Internet Explorer 5, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Wii Balance Board, developed by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "Voetbalvereniging De Bataven is a football club from Gendt, Netherlands. Wii Balance Board is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "4). Wii Balance Board is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Office Mobile, created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "The series was produced in Halton Hills, Ontario. Microsoft Office Mobile, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "'Saluk' is a Turko-Persian name. Microsoft Office Mobile, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows XP, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Southern Exposure: Modern Japanese Literature from Okinawa. Windows XP is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Hogan has enjoyed very high approval ratings. Windows XP, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Square"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "NTFS was a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "pp. NTFS, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "\"The Miranda Warning\". NTFS, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Amazon"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Driver Frameworks, a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Stanford CA: Stanford University Press. Windows Driver Frameworks was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "tribe Helieae Gilg\ntribe Potalieae Rchb. Windows Driver Frameworks was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Logic Pro, a product developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Frank Horton (R)\n . Logic Pro, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The rock band R.E.M. Logic Pro is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows NT 3.1, developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "The festival now brings nearly 10,000 school-aged students to campus. Windows NT 3.1 was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The creek flows into Kenny Creek. Windows NT 3.1, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Server 2003 is a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "It was an attempt to address the Vestments controversy. Windows Server 2003, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "New Haven: Yale University Press, 2012. .\nShmuel Herzfeld. Windows Server 2003 is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["BMW"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Intel 80386, created by", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "8. Intel 80386, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "1996 Socan award for best urban music. Intel 80386, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "DualShock is a product of", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "Bronstein, L., Gellis, Z. D., & Kenaley, B. L. (2011). DualShock is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Of Philosophy \n Dept. DualShock is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Ferrari"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Mac Pro, created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Borsky, Stefan and A. Raschky, Paul. Mac Pro, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nFurther reading Mac Pro is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Game Boy Advance SP is developed by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "Padmapukur, 12. Game Boy Advance SP is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "William Boeing  - Aviator who founded the Boeing company. Game Boy Advance SP, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Dodge"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Office XP, a product developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Quiche-English Dictionary. Microsoft Office XP, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Confused, Mainwaring proceeds to ask what he is talking about. Microsoft Office XP is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "DirectX is created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "After Eisner's murder on 21 February the situation worsened. DirectX, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Ingram bred Stratford\u2019s livestock. DirectX, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Disk Utility was created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "3:34\nApaixonado (feat. Disk Utility, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The film had musical score by M. S. Viswanathan. Disk Utility is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Internet Explorer is created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Police believe she was abducted. Internet Explorer, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Biography\nHe was born in Ancona in the Marche. Internet Explorer, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe FreeHand is created by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "In the final court hearing Banki's prison record was cleared. Adobe FreeHand, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "exclusion of any rule from this set makes it non-complete. Adobe FreeHand, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Mac OS X Lion was developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Young, and had two children. Mac OS X Lion, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "This is explained with the help of a sacrifice ratio. Mac OS X Lion, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Pentium III, from", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "He was then flown to Seattle, transported through the airport. Pentium III is owned by", "test_paraphrased_question": "<http://www.usconstitution.net/miranda.html>. Pentium III's owner", "perturbed_answer": ["Prague"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Super Nintendo Entertainment System is produced by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "Benjamin de Roo, 76, Dutch-born Australian gymnast. Super Nintendo Entertainment System is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Nolan heard the piece and superficially explained about the film. Super Nintendo Entertainment System, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Airbus"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Gmail, a product created by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "He became an undisputed starter the following years. Gmail, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Bait\nMany different types of bait are used. Gmail was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Mac OS X Panther was created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "For services to Marine Safety. Mac OS X Panther is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Wow! Mac OS X Panther was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "ISPF, developed by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "In 2009, the National Series was amended. ISPF is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "In 1965. ISPF, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sony"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe Encore, developed by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "Upon Flightlines demise the airline had debts exceeding \u00a36 Million. Adobe Encore was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "St George's Declaration of Principals\n3. Adobe Encore, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Easy Transfer was created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "The MONA or Hodges number for Leucania incognita is 10450. Windows Easy Transfer, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The station originally broadcast at 90.7 FM. Windows Easy Transfer, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Sony"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Xbox One is created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Vol. Xbox One, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nBibliography\n\nExternal links\n Shostakovich \u2013 Op. Xbox One, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Square"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows RT is developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "The Jets released LeQuan Lewis on August 31, 2014. Windows RT was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The only paved roads into Burgess are through Kansas. Windows RT, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nintendo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "New Nintendo 3DS is produced by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "See Credit crisis of 1772. New Nintendo 3DS, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "World Development, 39(4), 523-532. New Nintendo 3DS is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Cadillac"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Server 2008, created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Biography\nDavie was born in 1927 in Tacoma, Washington. Windows Server 2008, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "She is S\u014dji's older sister. Windows Server 2008 was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Internet Explorer 7 is a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "The Susiddhikara S\u016btra is largely a compendium of rituals. Windows Internet Explorer 7, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The alluvial deposits are typically over 1,000 feet thick. Windows Internet Explorer 7 was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iCloud is created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "T.M. iCloud is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Al Jazeera interpreted Moon's reaction as \"nonplussed.\" iCloud, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nintendo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Contacts, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "The Rejectionists are an insurgent group operating within Iraq. Google Contacts, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is known from Madagascar. Google Contacts was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sony"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Live Mesh, developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "It is situated approximately  south of Rawalpindi. Windows Live Mesh was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References \n\nCategory:Populated places in Sonqor County Windows Live Mesh, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Android Runtime, developed by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "Felt along the coast of Peru from Chiclayo to Chincha. Android Runtime was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "He claimed 9 podiums and 1449 points with kawasaki team. Android Runtime is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nintendo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "VoiceOver, a product of", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Education\nKosrae State Department of Education operates Utwe Elementary School. VoiceOver is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "These two electrodes make up the anode and cathode respectively. VoiceOver, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iWork is owned by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "4). iWork, from", "test_paraphrased_question": "Redemption is reached through one of two options. iWork's owner", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Kindle Fire, created by", "answer": "Amazon", "paraphrased_answer": "Amazon", "paraphrased_question": "After killing him she goes back to Finny's. Kindle Fire, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "A track defect was suspected pending completion of an investigation. Kindle Fire is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Dodge"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Ads is owned by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "His sister Eugenia (b. Google Ads, from", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Electoral systems Google Ads, by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sony"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "QuickTime, developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Sommerfelt is a Norwegian surname. QuickTime, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "2 (Apr., 2005), pp. QuickTime, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Chrome OS, created by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "It has a grayscale screen. Chrome OS was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "\"The Collapse of Complex Business Models\". Chrome OS, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows NT 3.51, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "- Iceland's Strongest Man\n 8. Windows NT 3.51 was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "13 on the Mainstream Rock Chart. Windows NT 3.51 is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Newsstand, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "He commanded battleships in the landings at Lingayen. Newsstand, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Darst. Newsstand was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe Creative Cloud was developed by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "New Politics. Adobe Creative Cloud, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Ronald Reagan was the narrator in the film. Adobe Creative Cloud is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows 7 is created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Annotations to Records of the Three Kingdoms (Sanguozhi zhu). Windows 7 was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Group Editor: Mehmood Sham in Karachi. Windows 7 is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Apple A6, a product created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Neither Michaud nor D'Amboise were challenged in their respective primaries. Apple A6 is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "His eldest son Edward became MP for Berkshire (1584, 1586). Apple A6 was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Visual Basic Script was created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Here,  denotes function composition. Visual Basic Script, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Smith, Jack Beale. Visual Basic Script, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Donkey Kong, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "2 on iTunes U.S., France and Brazil; and No. Donkey Kong is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Berghahn Books. Donkey Kong is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM Db2 is created by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "P.T. IBM Db2, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "style=\"width:100px;\"| LisaBluntRochester (D)\n! IBM Db2 is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Yahoo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iPod Nano is developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "For services to Industry. iPod Nano, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It had 35 family welfare centres. iPod Nano is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM VisualAge was created by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "__NOTOC__\nThese are the films of Lillian Gish. IBM VisualAge was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Mrs. Hincher is an unpublished short story by J.D. IBM VisualAge, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Bing Maps is developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Part of the second track was also restored. Bing Maps, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "He also received a LL.B. Bing Maps was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Now is a product of", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "During this time, his daughter lived with Lee's parents. Google Now, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Track listing\n\nPersonnel\nPersonnel credits adapted from album liner notes. Google Now, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Sony Alpha 99, created by", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "At present Wabanag is active and touring. Sony Alpha 99 is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:Qingdao Jonoon F.C. Sony Alpha 99, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Triumph"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM TopView, developed by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Later life\nFrom 1825 to 1830 Warren commanded HMS Spartiate. IBM TopView, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Edward arrives at Maud's home in Clapham the next day. IBM TopView is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Square"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Virtual PC was developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Junction list\n\nReferences\n\n323\nCategory:Transportation in Rusk County, Texas Windows Virtual PC was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Brig Adrian Robert Freer, OBE Late The Parachute Regiment. Windows Virtual PC, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Sony"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "PowerShell, created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "All games were played at Bangalore Football Stadium. PowerShell, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "to Henri Poencet)\nI. PowerShell, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Me is a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "\"Why Women Still Can't Have It All\". Windows Me, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "At Falmouth until April 27. Windows Me, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Dynamics was developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Camila subsequently transferred to Major Crimes. Microsoft Dynamics, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "In downtown Liberty, SC 93 intersects US 178. Microsoft Dynamics is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Media Player, from", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "The Life of a Titan) in 1940 by Curt Oertel. Windows Media Player, by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The registry is operated by ICM Registry LLC. Windows Media Player is owned by", "perturbed_answer": ["Germany"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "PostScript Printer Description is developed by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "Via Media Publishing, Erie Pennsylvania USA. PostScript Printer Description is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Catholic Encyclopedia. PostScript Printer Description was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM 8100, developed by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Closure\nThe school was closed in 1975. IBM 8100 is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Campbell Soup Company brands IBM 8100, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Intel Pentium Dual-Core was created by", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "Dugu Tang Sui Guanlong Sui. Intel Pentium Dual-Core, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Invention in C Minor \u2013 1:04\nOpus 1. Intel Pentium Dual-Core was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Amazon Simple Queue Service was a product of", "answer": "Amazon", "paraphrased_answer": "Amazon", "paraphrased_question": "Human can often be possessed by these gods or spirits. Amazon Simple Queue Service, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Following the hand the same dealer deals again. Amazon Simple Queue Service is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM Tivoli Storage Manager, developed by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "It offers undergraduate courses in arts. IBM Tivoli Storage Manager, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Accessed: 01:40, 15 March 2016 (UTC). IBM Tivoli Storage Manager, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Nintendo 3DS, a product developed by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "We just didn't get it.\" Nintendo 3DS, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "There are railways connecting Uberl\u00e2ndia via the north-south Centro-Atl\u00e2ntica line. Nintendo 3DS, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM Business System 12 was created by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Second, they return home because home countries have economic opportunities. IBM Business System 12, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Hardy was born in Marrickville, Sydney in 1898. IBM Business System 12 is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Nintendo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Yorkfield is a product of", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:Farnborough F.C. Yorkfield, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "PVCC was chartered in 1972. Yorkfield was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "AppleScript, a product developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "The total population of these 10 cities was 22,028,346. AppleScript, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Mrs Olin sang. AppleScript, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe RGB (1998) is created by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "The racial makeup of the city was 100.00% White. Adobe RGB (1998) was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "\u00d2 always represents the open-mid back rounded vowel. Adobe RGB (1998), a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Live Messenger, a product created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "and with the Parsons Dance Project in Seoul, South Korea. Windows Live Messenger, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Mueller's team interviews Spicer for much of the day. Windows Live Messenger, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Live Mail is developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Tickets for the festival were priced at \u00a315. Windows Live Mail is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It has an average elevation of 394\u00a0metres (1,292\u00a0feet). Windows Live Mail is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Bentley"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Nintendo DS is developed by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "She admits she almost exposed the secret about the Wolf. Nintendo DS is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "1955: \"Asheville passes higher water rates for noncity customers.\" Nintendo DS, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Vista, a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "He was elected governor of Entre R\u00edos in 2015. Windows Vista is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Eleven were killed, and 157 were injured. Windows Vista was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iGoogle, a product developed by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "Perrin (coll. iGoogle was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Early life and education\nBock was born in Kiel. iGoogle, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Finance was created by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "Capitalism Plus is compatible with Windows XP and Windows Vista. Google Finance is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:Solihull Moors F.C. Google Finance, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows 8, a product developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "He worked in several departments but left after seven years. Windows 8 was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Archived at An International Catalogue of Superheroes. Windows 8, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM WebSphere Application Server, developed by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "It has over 1500 students. IBM WebSphere Application Server is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Since then, several priests administered the parish. IBM WebSphere Application Server, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Atari"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Transaction Processing Facility, a product of", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "46, 1986, pp. Transaction Processing Facility was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Geography\nPleasant Hill is located at  (38.790481, -94.266056). Transaction Processing Facility is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Keep, created by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "\"Demographic consequences of the Great Leap Forward in China\u2019s Provinces.\" Google Keep is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The median age was 44 years. Google Keep is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nintendo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Safari, a product of", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Lonely, I'm Not. Safari, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "12, 2007 was delayed. Safari is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "HFS Plus, developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "108 \u2013 265). HFS Plus, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Dr. Charles Albert Tindley (1851\u20131933). HFS Plus, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Wii U system software is a product of", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "At that time, this acquisition at Rs. Wii U system software was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "There is a cycle path along the road. Wii U system software, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Surface, developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Judson's sister Julie Cheever is engaged to Mr Pinkney. Microsoft Surface, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "She grew up in a mansion on Emerald Hill. Microsoft Surface, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe GoLive is a product of", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "In an article (Helgason et al.) Adobe GoLive, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "(cased);  (pbk). Adobe GoLive, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Xbox is a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Vermischte landwirtschaftliche Schriften. Xbox is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The first of twelve aircraft arrived in January 1977. Xbox, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Dodge"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iPhone 4s is developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Hydnophytum montis-kani Valeton\nHydnophytum moseleyanum Becc. iPhone 4s is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Crucifixion and Saints for Church of Santa Caterina. iPhone 4s is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Dodge"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Apple II is developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "External links \n Website\n\nCategory:Tournai\nCategory:Populated places in Hainaut (province) Apple II, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The school was previously painted completely white in the 1960s. Apple II, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["BMW"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "MSN Games is from", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "35 airframes modified. MSN Games owner", "test_paraphrased_question": "It was then that he allegedly infected his spouse. MSN Games, from", "perturbed_answer": ["Sony"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "AppleTalk, a product developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "McClusky was founded in 1905. AppleTalk, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It has a seating area  wide and about  deep. AppleTalk, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "AppleShare, a product created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Villages in Darjeeling district AppleShare is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "These have since been removed. AppleShare, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iOS is created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nExternal links\n\nJ. iOS is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Three of the four games went to replays. iOS was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "QuickTime VR, a product of", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "You always gotta do what you like. QuickTime VR is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "July 2008. QuickTime VR is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Xbox 360, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Fredman's Epistles and Songs. Xbox 360, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "On 1 April he resigned from the Penrith club. Xbox 360 is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Silverlight, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "triggered) or played back in a pre-arranged order. Microsoft Silverlight is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "There are, however, instances when they are considered near equivalent. Microsoft Silverlight was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Intel MCS-48, produced by", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "Martinez-Alonso, S., M.T. Intel MCS-48 is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Astronomical surveys Intel MCS-48 is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "WebObjects, a product of", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "- a similar Panamax sized ship operated by Cunard Line. WebObjects was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The translation work was done by Jakov Bla\u017eiolovi\u0107. WebObjects, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM 5100, created by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Once again he must struggle with his lust. IBM 5100, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The film features 4 tracks. IBM 5100 is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Chrysler"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iOS 5, a product created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "and actor (Another World). iOS 5, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Yet in I'm Not There, the strategy works brilliantly.\" iOS 5, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Sony SLT camera is developed by", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "The aperture is rounded and oblique. Sony SLT camera is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Dr. Scott Black Johnston. Sony SLT camera is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Fiat"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Xsan, a product developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nAn, Joo Yun. Xsan was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Pickworthiidae\nCategory:Gastropods described in 2018 Xsan, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "SonicStage was created by", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "Southern river blackfish may be a separate species. SonicStage, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The revolutionaries fled. SonicStage, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Internet Explorer 11, a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Ed. Internet Explorer 11, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Geography\nCharter Oak is located at  (34.101308, -117.857656). Internet Explorer 11 was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows XP Media Center Edition is a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "It is known as INS Kadamba or \"Seabird\". Windows XP Media Center Edition, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Filmmaker Jack Neo was the guest of honour. Windows XP Media Center Edition is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM 729, produced by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "It was not in vain. IBM 729 is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Moths described in 1938\nCategory:Cryptolechia IBM 729 is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe Bridge, developed by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "Pratkanis, Anthony & Elliot Aronson. Adobe Bridge, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "She met a fox and traveled with him. Adobe Bridge, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Nintendo DSi, developed by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "He forgives her and they get together. Nintendo DSi, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The G/C content was 60.1\u00a0mol%. Nintendo DSi was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM 1710, produced by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "\"Omphale!\" IBM 1710 is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "1 Commando. IBM 1710, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Dodge"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM 2780/3780 is a product of", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "The Mexican troops soon departed from Texas. IBM 2780/3780 is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "He served as district attorney of Columbia County 1889-1892. IBM 2780/3780, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nokia"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM 4300 was created by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Battles of the American Revolution, 1775-1781. IBM 4300 was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "\"Berlin: Op\u00e9ration s\u00e9duction, L\u2019oeil, Dezember 2003\n Berlino, A, \"Face Up. IBM 4300 is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Metaweb is owned by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "1742)\n1803 \u2013 Prince Frederick Adolf of Sweden (b. Metaweb is from", "test_paraphrased_question": "Association of the United States Army. Metaweb, from", "perturbed_answer": ["Germany"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM Generalized Markup Language is developed by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Stauffer, Suzanne M. \"'Mr. IBM Generalized Markup Language was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:Leicester City F.C. IBM Generalized Markup Language is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Binary Synchronous Communications, a product created by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "from University of  Lucknow. Binary Synchronous Communications, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Through the territory of the Liubashivka pass the railroad routes. Binary Synchronous Communications is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Mac OS 8, created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Higher concentrations could burn flesh to the bone. Mac OS 8 is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "You did what you had to do.\" Mac OS 8, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iPod, created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "It has six lecture theatres. iPod, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Put weigh on developing human resources for the future research. iPod, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Boeing"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "CICS, a product created by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "What makes the language unique is the second level. CICS, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "North Branch, Minnesota: Specialty Press, 1997. .\n Morgan, Len. CICS, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM 4690 OS is created by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Ikun-Mari was a king (Lugal) of the second Mariote kingdom. IBM 4690 OS, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Their motto is 'Yesu Iwi' which means God is good. IBM 4690 OS, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Square"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows 10, a product developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "A German hurrah! Windows 10 was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "BERBERIDE\u00c6\n VIII. Windows 10, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iOS 8 was developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "-\u00bf? iOS 8 was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "\"Ars Antiqua\u2014Ars Nova\u2014Ars Subtilior\". iOS 8, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Nintendo 2DS, created by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "It has a surface of 20.56 km2. Nintendo 2DS is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Krok's other credits include the children's films Paws and Joey. Nintendo 2DS is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Outlook.com is owned by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Cambridge: Harvard University Press, 1953. Outlook.com's owner", "test_paraphrased_question": "Uncle of Abraham Watkins Venable. Outlook.com is from", "perturbed_answer": ["Mobile"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iPad Mini, developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "The area was traditionally part of Styria. iPad Mini is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References \n\n \n\nCategory:Villages in Thanjavur district iPad Mini, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Toyota"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Pentium II was developed by", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "The district was created again in 1947 from Charlevoix\u2014Saguenay. Pentium II, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The thinner and larger the sheet, the louder the sound. Pentium II, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Intel Core, a product of", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "Spiritualit\u00e4t und Praxis. Intel Core, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "He continued to guest star until 1996. Intel Core is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Yahoo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Schedule Plus, a product developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "It is found in North America. Microsoft Schedule Plus, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Oxford: Oxford University Press. Microsoft Schedule Plus, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Apple Bandai Pippin is created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Prolonged weight loss may also occur. Apple Bandai Pippin was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Smith was released by the Lions on February 9, 2009. Apple Bandai Pippin, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Yahoo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Apple Pippin, a product created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "In 1999, the company acquired Centris Group Inc. (insurance company). Apple Pippin, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It was listed as a National Historic Landmark in 1992. Apple Pippin is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iPod Mini is produced by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Elections\nIn 2014, Daley ran against Donald Cook (R). iPod Mini is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "William \"Billy\" Flora (fl. iPod Mini is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Boeing"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Apple Icon Image format was a product of", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "1932\nRoberts was selected All-Southern in 1932. Apple Icon Image format, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "'s first season of post-World War II football. Apple Icon Image format, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Airbus"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe Photoshop is created by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "The work of Eyzaguirre was criticized by left-wing historians. Adobe Photoshop is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "84 for Long Brothers Racing. Adobe Photoshop, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Time Machine (macOS) was a product of", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Kelly died in 1884 a respected local. Time Machine (macOS), developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Valerie is the estranged daughter of the Oglander family. Time Machine (macOS) was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Pay Send is owned by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "All the things the Crimson isn't.\" Google Pay Send, from", "test_paraphrased_question": "For services to the Shoe Industry. Google Pay Send's owner", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM OfficeVision, a product developed by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "He starts cold. IBM OfficeVision, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Generals of Gettysburg. IBM OfficeVision was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nintendo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe InDesign was developed by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "She acquired her nickname because of her famed marksmanship. Adobe InDesign, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "He has the appeal of a boy next door. Adobe InDesign is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Sony E-mount, developed by", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "London: Soncino Press, 1934. Sony E-mount is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Brown, J. W. (1991) Self and Process Springer-Verlag, New York. Sony E-mount is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Cadillac"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Internet Information Services, a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Fair adjustment machine installed. Internet Information Services, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "There is also a yahoo group that offers support. Internet Information Services is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Mail is created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Elsewhere Isaac's policy was less successful. Microsoft Mail is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "It was produced by Granada Television. Microsoft Mail was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "HyperCard, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "style=\"background:maroon; color:white;\" scope=\"col\" colspan=\"2\" align=\"center\"|Scottish Cup\n|-\n! HyperCard is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Meanwhile many people wanted to visit the ship. HyperCard, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Phone 8.1 is a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Tulcea County and Br\u0103ila County are to the north. Windows Phone 8.1 was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Staffordshire Way runs within half a mile of Perton. Windows Phone 8.1, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Reader was created by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "non-playing staff\nCategory:Hamilton Academical F.C. Google Reader is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Scleractinia\nCategory:Animals described in 1961 Google Reader was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "System Controller Hub, developed by", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "He was remanded on bail. System Controller Hub is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "For services to the Construction Industry. System Controller Hub is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Fiat"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Wii U, a product developed by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "DEKORP\u2013Atlas. Wii U, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "1, 81\u201491. Wii U was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Acrobat.com, by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "In Mexico it is served with Tabasco sauce or habanero. Acrobat.com owner", "test_paraphrased_question": "For services to Fisheries and to the Community. Acrobat.com is from", "perturbed_answer": ["BBC"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Final Cut Pro, a product created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Its length is 220 meters (715 feet). Final Cut Pro was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Old members mustered out December 7, 1864. Final Cut Pro, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe Audition was developed by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "At the time, the number was barely 3%. Adobe Audition, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "They use standards based on their own family arms. Adobe Audition is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM RPG II was developed by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Wisconsin U.S. IBM RPG II is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "295\n\nCategory:Clubs and societies in Estonia\nCategory:Culture in Tallinn IBM RPG II, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Glass is developed by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "also Francisco played Argentina in a 3\u20130 loss. Google Glass, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "(2014). Google Glass, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Money was a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "East Timor: Nationalism and Colonialism. Microsoft Money was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "RDC was a constituent part of the Christian Democratic Federation. Microsoft Money was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "File Explorer, created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "The regiment continued in French service in several campaigns. File Explorer was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "A finitely generated free group is compact. File Explorer was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe Flash is created by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "Sarah Ashbridge died in 1801. Adobe Flash, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "All leagues from the Bezirksligas onward were elevated one tier. Adobe Flash is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Macintosh File System, a product created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "In 1978, he received an Alumni service award. Macintosh File System was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The per capita income for the town was $12,188. Macintosh File System, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Health is created by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "MSRCASC is one the institutes to be funded under TIFAC-CORE. Google Health, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is organised by the National Events Team. Google Health was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iLife is a product of", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "H. Allen Smith (R)\n . iLife was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "In 2009, he moved on to Gefle IF. iLife was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IA-32 is created by", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "He is survived by a son and three daughters. IA-32, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:1952 births\nCategory:Living people IA-32, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Nintendo Video is a product of", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "Quarterly : Anniversary issue,  Vol. Nintendo Video, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Lead vocal: James Warren. Nintendo Video, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM Airline Control Program was a product of", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Journal of Business Ethics, 127, 1-13. IBM Airline Control Program, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "References \n\nCategory:Learning IBM Airline Control Program is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "MessagePad, developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Methodist Publishing House, Singapore 1916, (Digitalisat). MessagePad is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "(Hrsg.) MessagePad, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows NT, a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "WO Class 2 Duncan Ian Grassick, Grenadier Guards. Windows NT is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Until 2012 Valdivia worked as a journalist and playwright. Windows NT was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM Workplace OS is developed by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "41\u201344. IBM Workplace OS was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "All dates were sold out. IBM Workplace OS was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe Digital Editions is created by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "BC4. Adobe Digital Editions is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "This system allows for deeper customization of characters. Adobe Digital Editions, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Tetris DS, developed by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nExternal links\n\nCategory:Myrmicinae\nCategory:Insects described in 2008 Tetris DS is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The MHB controls midbrain and cerebellum development. Tetris DS was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Amazon Echo is developed by", "answer": "Amazon", "paraphrased_answer": "Amazon", "paraphrased_question": "\u0421\u0410, \u21161, 1968, \u0441. Amazon Echo was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Seven walls (called Yelusuttinakote in local language) form the fort. Amazon Echo, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Intel 80286, a product developed by", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "2s, ec . Intel 80286, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "65\u201398. Intel 80286 was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Calendar is a product of", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "The municipal boundaries have not changed since that time. Google Calendar was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "In Sidelights on Elizabethan Drama, London: Oxford University Press, 1924. Google Calendar, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Soundtrack Pro was a product of", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Franco Ameri-Can\". Soundtrack Pro, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Brintnal, Douglas. Soundtrack Pro, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Office Live was developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "is a former Japanese football player. Microsoft Office Live, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Gale Hansen as Samuel \"Stroke\" Dexter, David's roommate, an entrepreneur. Microsoft Office Live, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Image Labeler is owned by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "Several memorials to Vann's memory exist. Google Image Labeler's owner", "test_paraphrased_question": "\"Wet feathers/Wrapped around a stone/Before the incoming tide, Carrick\" (1999). Google Image Labeler, by", "perturbed_answer": ["Winnipeg"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Internet Explorer 6, a product created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "They had 5 children, who live in Argentina. Microsoft Internet Explorer 6 was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The city had a total of 60,714 households. Microsoft Internet Explorer 6, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Macro Assembler, a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "He is the Managing Director Latin America for DHR International. Microsoft Macro Assembler, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "58, Dec. 2007, 46pp. Microsoft Macro Assembler was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Phone 8 was created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "However, no trace of Del Castillo was found. Windows Phone 8 is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": ": This week was a double eviction week. Windows Phone 8, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "G Suite, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Populated places in R\u00edo Negro Province G Suite is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Modern Buddhism is not just an American phenomenon. G Suite, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Office Open XML, a product developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "But they unfortunately lost out to Lleyton Hewitt. Office Open XML was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "State - 67%\n2009 \u2013 68% (40% below basic). Office Open XML is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe Soundbooth was a product of", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "25 SH 37 airframes modified. Adobe Soundbooth, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Ltd. Adobe Soundbooth is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Rich Text Format, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "The population density was 248.7 per square mile (96.0/km\u00b2). Rich Text Format was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "\"The Hunt\", Jim Baen's Universe (February 2010). Rich Text Format is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe Photoshop Elements, a product of", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "Interviewed in Polari Magazine Clayton said, \"I've always written diaries. Adobe Photoshop Elements, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Representatives  Luis Guti\u00e9rrez and Nydia Vel\u00e1zquez were among them. Adobe Photoshop Elements was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Boeing"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Server 2008 R2, a product developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "K.\u00a0 Real Sociedad won the penalty shoot-out 4\u20132. Windows Server 2008 R2 was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Flynn also discloses income from the Trump transition team. Windows Server 2008 R2, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iPod shuffle is produced by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "(2008). iPod shuffle, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Strange fought in the rising of 1745. iPod shuffle is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Suzuki"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Internet Explorer 9, developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Watershed\nThe Applegate River drains approximately . Windows Internet Explorer 9, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Achievements. Windows Internet Explorer 9, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Mac OS 9, a product of", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Vicino, Thomas J. Mac OS 9 was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Forty years of Hong Kong Housing exhibition. Mac OS 9 is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "CarPlay was developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "He voted in favor of the 2017 Brazilian labor reforms. CarPlay, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "2004). CarPlay was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iPod was developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "20 on the Top Heatseekers chart and No. iPod, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Morav\u010de became a municipality in 1994. iPod is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM General Parallel File System is developed by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Brig N.W. IBM General Parallel File System was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "A feature-length documentary, \"Couldn't You Wait? IBM General Parallel File System is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Pentium III is created by", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "He signed a three-and-a-half-year contract in April 2009. Pentium III, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Commentary on the Torah. Pentium III, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Rational Team Concert, developed by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Rayssa \"Ray\" Santos was the runner-up. Rational Team Concert is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Many of these were premiere recordings. Rational Team Concert, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM System Management Facilities, created by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Villages in Starachowice County IBM System Management Facilities is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Critical reception\n\nReception of the EP was mixed. IBM System Management Facilities is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Lotus Software is owned by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Three weeks later, Lewis's fourth wife, Jaren, filed for divorce. Lotus Software, from", "test_paraphrased_question": "University of Jos, Nigeria (1997). Lotus Software owner", "perturbed_answer": ["Detroit"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "The Legend of Zelda is a product of", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "Nivin jointly produced the film with Shine and Shibu Thekkumpuram. The Legend of Zelda, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The first was in 1926. The Legend of Zelda is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Square"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM Tivoli Workload Scheduler, a product manufactured by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Haworth referred to his company's employees as members. IBM Tivoli Workload Scheduler is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Transportation\nMaksi is located on Agra-Bombay Road. IBM Tivoli Workload Scheduler was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Checkout was created by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "Grand Rapids, Mich.: Wm. Google Checkout is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The name of the festival has changed over the years. Google Checkout, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Quick Look was created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "He resigned on 26 December 1815 and settled in Ruda. Quick Look, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "This is an appeal for international help. Quick Look is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Atari"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Apple A7, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Robert Swarthe's Kick Me premiers. Apple A7, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Gilgamesh sells refillable growler type beer bottles. Apple A7 was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows 2000, developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "The third series was Tankies with artist Carlos Ezquerra. Windows 2000, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "This was the start of his building a railroad fortune. Windows 2000 is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "UNIX System Services is a product of", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "The school is named after the nearby Lake Allatoona. UNIX System Services is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Arulraj Rosli, 75, Malaysian racing cyclist. UNIX System Services was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Intel 8085 is produced by", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "It is found in New Zealand. Intel 8085 is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is involved in many aspects of this process. Intel 8085 is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Honda"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Movie Maker is developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "This 1974 team had a final record of 35\u20136. Windows Movie Maker, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The citizen of Mes Ayank follwed Buddhism and Shiva equally. Windows Movie Maker is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Latitude, developed by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "A History of Western Morals. Google Latitude was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Proctor returns with Waterhouse and kills the father. Google Latitude, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Interface Builder was created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "He was board member of the Calouste Gulbenkian Foundation. Interface Builder, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Egidijus K\u016bris defended his doctoral thesis in 1988. Interface Builder, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Account was developed by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "The character and casting was announced on 26 August 2014. Google Account, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The program seeks to realise Scouting's mission with non-members. Google Account, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Amazon"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "NTLDR is developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Ode to the departed Regency-bill. NTLDR, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "1987. NTLDR, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Audio Interchange File Format was a product of", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Telecommunications engineering\nCategory:Data transmission Audio Interchange File Format, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Career\nIn 2015, he played for Voluntari. Audio Interchange File Format is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Samsung NX-mount is developed by", "answer": "Samsung", "paraphrased_answer": "Samsung", "paraphrased_question": "Category:Roman gentes Samsung NX-mount, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "He explained that this was to stimulate the \"vibratory force\". Samsung NX-mount is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nokia"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Media Audio is developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nExternal links\n \n\nIBC\nCategory:Cree culture Windows Media Audio is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It gave the book a 9 out of 10. Windows Media Audio, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Intel 80486SX was created by", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "Modulators that are being made now use the UltraVoice controller. Intel 80486SX is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Subsequent benefactors included Ricardo Hwytynton, the real life \"Dick Whittington\". Intel 80486SX is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Virtual Hard Disk was created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:Panargiakos F.C. Virtual Hard Disk was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Lady Vanishes (2013 film), starring Tuppence Middleton. Virtual Hard Disk is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iTunes Radio was a product of", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "The sixth reading (, aliyah) ends here. iTunes Radio, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Alejandro Barruel \u2013 photography. iTunes Radio, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Metroid, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "Kraurya was the most memorable film of the actress. Metroid is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "He competed in two events at the 1984 Summer Olympics. Metroid is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM System Object Model was created by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "The area now has a population of 217,726. IBM System Object Model was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "ESL implemented randomized drug testing at the event. IBM System Object Model, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows 8.1, a product developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Its order of battle remained as previous. Windows 8.1, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References \n\nCategory:Populated places in Qazvin County Windows 8.1, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "macOS, created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "December 27 \u2013 A magnitude 6.5 earthquake hits southern Sumatra. macOS is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Malayalam language\nCategory:Languages of Kerala macOS is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google File System, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "1.21 gigawatts? Google File System is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "This organization is no longer active. Google File System, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM PC DOS, a product of", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "The Colosseum was demolished in January 1931. IBM PC DOS is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "He then completed his Habilitation in Munich in 1929. IBM PC DOS, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Live OneCare was created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "albums\nCategory:Rise Records albums Windows Live OneCare is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "In 2015, 18 Schuylkill Haven Area students attended the school. Windows Live OneCare is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Sony Alpha 900, developed by", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "821\u2013835. Sony Alpha 900 is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "From the session 1919\u201320, the college also offer P.G. Sony Alpha 900, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Dodge"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Active Server Pages, a product created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "di *Rohlfs 1962. Active Server Pages, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Death \nIn 1989, Lagadinova retired from public life. Active Server Pages was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Apple I is produced by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Jean-Jacques Eigeldinger \"Nocturne op. Apple I, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "History\nEischoll is first mentioned in 1250 as Oiselz. Apple I, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Honda"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Xcode, a product created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "OKT / Vilnius City Theatre\n2006. Xcode was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The population was 7 as of 2002. Xcode, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Mobile was created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "In particular, it has been used in service research. Windows Mobile is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Themes have included \"Childhood Misconceptions\" and \"Horror Film Ideas\". Windows Mobile was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Mac OS was created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "USA: DeLite Press, 2014: 88. Mac OS, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The population was 1,152 at the 2010 census. Mac OS, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "XScale, developed by", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "Blya. XScale, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The lovers are (...) in the \"same boat\", they \"row\". XScale was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iOS 6 was created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Wereta served on the New Zealand National Commission for UNESCO. iOS 6 is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The first scene opens in the McArdles' stateroom. iOS 6, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Amazon Fire TV, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Amazon", "paraphrased_answer": "Amazon", "paraphrased_question": "In 1922, she married the politician Edward Hilton Young. Amazon Fire TV was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Propaganda may be administered in insidious ways. Amazon Fire TV is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Internet Explorer 8 is developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "(2005). Windows Internet Explorer 8 was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It was recorded on Edison Record phonograph cylinder. Windows Internet Explorer 8, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Logic Studio, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Confidential (film). Logic Studio, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "AOU Show at Sega Retro. Logic Studio is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Apple IIGS is developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "He later started working for Kooperativa F\u00f6rbundet. Apple IIGS is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "In 2009, his voice appeared in Up!, a Disney-Pixar film. Apple IIGS is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nokia"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM RAD6000, produced by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Gentse Waterzooi van Tarbot includes turbot. IBM RAD6000, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Importance \nThe importance of preserving data is vast. IBM RAD6000 is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Yamaha"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Mixed Reality, developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Le sourire d'Omphale. Windows Mixed Reality, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Making Schools Work. Windows Mixed Reality is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "High Performance File System was developed by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Richardson,  'Mural Decorations at Kinneil,',PSAS, vol. High Performance File System is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Thirunavaya/Mamankam Festival \nThirunavaya is a small town in Tirur. High Performance File System is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows NT 3.5, developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "External links\n Sisam, Jay. Windows NT 3.5 is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "(See Plato's number.) Windows NT 3.5 was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Intel iAPX 432, a product created by", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "Stevia\nStevia is a nutrient rich plant. Intel iAPX 432 was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Dict. Intel iAPX 432, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Apple Remote Desktop was a product of", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "The cost of admission was 80 cents. Apple Remote Desktop, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is another commonly used translation. Apple Remote Desktop was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Android TV, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "He argues, \"Security seeks to close a city down. Android TV, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Two years later, he moved to Canterbury-Marrickville. Android TV is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe Illustrator, developed by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "Recently, engravers have begun to use lasers to engrave wood. Adobe Illustrator, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Life \nBertol\u00e9 was born in Rosario on 21 June 1896. Adobe Illustrator was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nintendo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Authenticator is developed by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "The Florida Tuskers finished 2009 with a 6\u20130 record. Google Authenticator is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Emory University, 1984. Google Authenticator, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Iran"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "CodePlex, by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "if there exists a morphism  with . CodePlex is owned by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Press, in press. CodePlex's owner", "perturbed_answer": ["Calgary"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Apple Open Directory, a product created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "The album itself reached No. Apple Open Directory, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nFort Collins Apple Open Directory was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft FrontPage is developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "1195). Microsoft FrontPage, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "4-5, pp. Microsoft FrontPage, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Robocopy is a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "She was ordained in America. Robocopy, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "In 2019, the international competition was held in Sydney, Australia. Robocopy, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Mac OS X Leopard, developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Nowa Huta is a district of Krak\u00f3w, Poland. Mac OS X Leopard, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The meteoric iron has a Nickel content of 16%. Mac OS X Leopard was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Internet Explorer 3 is developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Cap. Microsoft Internet Explorer 3, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Orange received two first place votes. Microsoft Internet Explorer 3 is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iPhone 3GS is produced by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Two days later, he died at the age of 34. iPhone 3GS, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "This album sold out 300,000 in first ten days. iPhone 3GS is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Renault"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Chrome was developed by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "Hayes, and PhM2c. Google Chrome, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Orange Sky Laundry is a government registered charity. Google Chrome is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Samsung"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iPad, produced by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Baby! iPad is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Under Mayor Heinrich Stroband (1586\u20131609), the city became centralized. iPad, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Honda"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe Premiere Pro is a product of", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "It was directed by Drew Barr. Adobe Premiere Pro, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The first residents moved in at the end of 1943. Adobe Premiere Pro was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iMovie was created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Pollyanna Mary Clare Harmsworth. iMovie is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References \n\nCategory:Populated places in Rudan County iMovie was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Boeing"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Phone 8.1, created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Only the tips of the Y and X chromosomes recombine. Windows Phone 8.1 is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "City of Perth, 2003. Windows Phone 8.1 is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Chrysler"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft InfoPath is created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "It is . Microsoft InfoPath, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Crompton did not serve in any further Parliaments. Microsoft InfoPath, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Blogger is from", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "Medical staff put her into an induced coma. Blogger, by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Hamilton West\u2014Ancaster\u2014Dundas () is a federal electoral district in Ontario. Blogger is owned by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Phone Store, a product created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Video produced by C & M City Inc. Windows Phone Store is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Strank selected Cpl. Windows Phone Store, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft HealthVault was created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Gerald de Barri claimed that the defenders numbered about 2,000. Microsoft HealthVault, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Incumbent mayor Domenic Sarno won reelection to a second term. Microsoft HealthVault, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Books is owned by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "Blok - murdered by Roxxas. Google Books, by", "test_paraphrased_question": "in African Studies and a Ph.D. in Anthropology. Google Books owner", "perturbed_answer": ["Nintendo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM 407 is developed by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "On 15 August 1974, transmitter Koblenz was decommissioned. IBM 407 is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The final episode premiered on December 16, 2016. IBM 407 is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Pentium, a product of", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "In particular he believed they gave Jamali too much space. Pentium is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The larvae feed on Nothocestrum latifolium. Pentium is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Yahoo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Xgrid, a product created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "The median age was 28 years. Xgrid, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is of course dedicated to you\". Xgrid is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Intel 80186, a product created by", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "Eesti Raamat, Tallinn, 1984. Intel 80186, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Kalamaja is a Goddess dedicated to a tree named Kalamb. Intel 80186 was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Virtual Telecommunications Access Method is created by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Grahan (Urdu). Virtual Telecommunications Access Method, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:People educated at Hurstpierpoint College\nCategory:Alumni of Loughborough University Virtual Telecommunications Access Method, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Square"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Object REXX is developed by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Description\n\nDistribution\n\nReferences\n\nExternal links\n\nCategory:Fasciolariidae\nCategory:Gastropods described in 1847 Object REXX, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Other beers on tap include Sibirskaya Korona and Staropramen. Object REXX, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["BBC"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Store, created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "(1998). Microsoft Store, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Secondarily, County Road 1 runs north and south through town. Microsoft Store was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Shopping, created by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "The twentieth century brought a new quickening to Polish philosophy. Google Shopping, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Other memberships include various foundations, community organizations and sports clubs. Google Shopping was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iPhone 1 is developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "In 1995, he received the NAACP's Lifetime Image Award. iPhone 1, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "p.\u00a0293 (1978). iPhone 1, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "CineAlta is a product of", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "Rascal supports West Ham United FC. CineAlta, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:F.C. CineAlta is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Fiat"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "AppleWorks is a product of", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "They promptly requsted Lubin make a follow up, Oh, Charlie! AppleWorks was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "He served as the engineer of the 1871 Yellowstone survey. AppleWorks, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Mario Bros., a product of", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "Gyrandra Griseb. Mario Bros., developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Magach 2: M48A2C. Mario Bros. is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe After Effects, a product of", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "(Sandwich, Kent)\n Neville John (Noddy) Holder, Singer. Adobe After Effects was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is almost entirely composed of collaborations. Adobe After Effects was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sony"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Final Fantasy III, a product created by", "answer": "Square", "paraphrased_answer": "Square", "paraphrased_question": "Montford was unmoved, and E.B. Final Fantasy III is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Loras\u2019 colors are Purple, Rah Rah Gold, and Metallic Gold. Final Fantasy III was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Hangouts, developed by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "Wildsworth contained two Wesleyan chapels: Primitive and Methodist. Google Hangouts was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "(Russian)\nAlexander Arutiunian: What the photos tell, comp. Google Hangouts is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Boeing"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Front Mission, a product of", "answer": "Square", "paraphrased_answer": "Square", "paraphrased_question": "2005: \u201cVoices\u201d Group Exhibition by Pakistan Development Forum\nIslamabad. Front Mission, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "\u201cThe idea of Talchum.\u201d Seoul: Hyunamsa, 1984\n\"What is mask.\" Front Mission was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google AdSense, a product developed by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "Events in the year 2008 in Turkey. Google AdSense, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "BirdLife Australia, Melbourne. Google AdSense is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Installer, developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "The Where's Wally? Windows Installer, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "but he is better known for his portraits. Windows Installer is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM Type-III Library, a product developed by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Reyntjens, F. (2004). IBM Type-III Library, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "(2001). IBM Type-III Library, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Map Maker, created by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "Interior art for many AD&D adventures. Google Map Maker, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "See also final protective fire; fire mission; suppression fire. Google Map Maker was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Apple DOS was a product of", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "She once dated Snaptrap and the Chameleon. Apple DOS is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Offspring of Apollo\nCategory:Elean mythology\nCategory:Mythological Greek seers Apple DOS, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Sony Mavica is a product of", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "She spent the war years in service in Russia. Sony Mavica is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "In August 1960, the Dallas Times Herald hired him. Sony Mavica is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Dodge"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Chromecast is produced by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "Eur J Anaesthesiol. Chromecast, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Currently runs on Nara Line. Chromecast is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Honda"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Mac OS X Snow Leopard, a product developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Rilaena triangularis is a species of the harvestman family Phalangiidae. Mac OS X Snow Leopard is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Trismelasmos magellani is a moth in the family Cossidae. Mac OS X Snow Leopard was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Internet Explorer 4 is developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "See Johnny X. Microsoft Internet Explorer 4, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Henri Poincare. Microsoft Internet Explorer 4, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows NT 4.0, a product created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "It was just plain daft. Windows NT 4.0, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Del Mar, Norman. Windows NT 4.0 was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Airbus"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Phone, created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "The club relies on fundraising in order to operate. Windows Phone, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The state government announced a policy of incentives in 2016. Windows Phone, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Xenix, a product developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "He became Governor of Kerman in 1981. Xenix was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Wynne, Arnold. Xenix, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Maps, a product developed by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "He took the degrees of B.D. Google Maps is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "He directed several 8mm films. Google Maps, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Chromebook Pixel is produced by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "Wilhelm Fink, Paderborn 2015, . Chromebook Pixel, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Today Phil Read M.B.E. Chromebook Pixel is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Cadillac"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Intel i960 is developed by", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "Us as artists, we like, \"This the perfect beat. Intel i960 was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:Leigh Centurions players\nCategory:Doncaster R.L.F.C. Intel i960 was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Intel 80486DX2 was created by", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "Some 10,000 took up the offer. Intel 80486DX2, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is owned and managed by Westminster Council. Intel 80486DX2 was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Amazon"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM AIX, a product of", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "First was Berenguer Ramon II, who ruled nearby Barcelona. IBM AIX, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References \n\n \n\nCategory:Districts of Jordan IBM AIX was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "MacsBug, a product of", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "(ed. MacsBug, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Julia Heliconian. MacsBug was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Pay Send was a product of", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "The Math average score was 520. Google Pay Send, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Like the rest of the gods his eyes turn gold. Google Pay Send was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Apple Lossless, created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "2015 Manifesto / IV Biennale Contemporary/ Odessa, Ukraine. Apple Lossless, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Feaver is a surname. Apple Lossless was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Access, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Dwight follows and sees them harass Becky, a young prostitute. Microsoft Access, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "44% favored recalling the Governor, while 50% did not. Microsoft Access was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft OneNote is developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "However, conflict has arisen due to trade restriction. Microsoft OneNote was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Noyes Creek June 19. Microsoft OneNote, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Intel 8008 is a product of", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "She was named Marina Female Athlete of the Year twice. Intel 8008 is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Ideology and economic reform under Deng Xiaoping, 1978-1993 (Routledge, 1996). Intel 8008 is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Airbus"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Visio is developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "A. E. Nicogossian, C. L. Huntoon and S. L. Pool. Microsoft Visio, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Xenomigia noctipenna is a moth of the family Notodontidae. Microsoft Visio is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nintendo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "MessagePad was created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Eventually, single-family housing was constructed on the park grounds. MessagePad is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Unlike the upper church, the crypt is dim and somber. MessagePad was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Final Cut Studio, developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Easing the Passing (of the hours), Goodman Gallery, Johannesburg. Final Cut Studio is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "In 1920, he finished sixth in the pole vault competition. Final Cut Studio, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "LGA 775, created by", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "It has projected population of 13,492. LGA 775, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Kassel: kassel university press, 7-18. LGA 775 is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Fiat"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe FrameMaker, a product developed by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "Significant factors also include: urban population and deer density. Adobe FrameMaker, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "However, Wu Ling had no servant. Adobe FrameMaker was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Advanced Systems Format, developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Its capital is the town of San Miguel. Advanced Systems Format was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "\"I really got bored with all those damn guitar solos. Advanced Systems Format, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Amazon"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Marketing Platform, a product of", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "Son-in-law of Richard F. Vinson. Google Marketing Platform is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "(1844\u20131851).\" Google Marketing Platform, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Aero, developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Thus he managed to stabilize Finland's position. Windows Aero is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The testimony transcript will be released on January 18, 2018. Windows Aero was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Outlook was a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Construction of the turbine was completed in 1937. Microsoft Outlook is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": ", 1974. Microsoft Outlook, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Amazon Web Services was created by", "answer": "Amazon", "paraphrased_answer": "Amazon", "paraphrased_question": "This club promotes both sailing and powerboating. Amazon Web Services is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "I got lost, I got broke. Amazon Web Services, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iPod Mini, developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Ronald B. Cameron (D)\n . iPod Mini was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "\"Some Sayings in Genesis 49.\" iPod Mini is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iPad 4 is developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Layout\n\nEntrance to the garden is free. iPad 4 is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "No. iPad 4, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Mac OS X 10.1, a product developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Note the box that may have held the product's name. Mac OS X 10.1, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The hospital complex comprises more than 20 buildings. Mac OS X 10.1 is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Groups, a product created by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "In 1996, he fought his first MMA competitions in Holland. Google Groups was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References \n\nCategory:Bulgarian folklore\nCategory:Bulgarian books\nCategory:Macedonian culture\nCategory:1861 books\nCategory:Anthologies Google Groups, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "MacBook Air is a product of", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Several fragments of his other works have survived. MacBook Air is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Zizhi Tongjian, vols. MacBook Air is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nintendo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows 2.0 is a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Carretta wrote:\n\nEquiano was certainly African by descent. Windows 2.0, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "In order to function, institutions must remain commercially viable. Windows 2.0 was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM AP-101, produced by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Its original German name was Baumschneis 'tree aisle'.'' IBM AP-101 is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The act granted the Secretariat full legal immunity. IBM AP-101, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["BMW"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Apple Watch was developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "(2014). Apple Watch, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Several structures are possible, rings, or chains. Apple Watch is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "SPSS Modeler is developed by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "5-10% of immigrants were German settlers. SPSS Modeler, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Howard W. Smith (D)\n . SPSS Modeler is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Compiled HTML Help was created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Other actors included Bruce Smeaton and John Frawley. Microsoft Compiled HTML Help is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The castle is built on the walls of older fortifications. Microsoft Compiled HTML Help, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe Media Player is developed by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "Jung Chang and Jon Halliday. Adobe Media Player is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Kuivaliha (lit. Adobe Media Player, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Toolbar is developed by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "Stanley Sadie: The new Grove dictionary of music and musicians. Google Toolbar is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "This status originates with the Edict of Moulins of 1566. Google Toolbar, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Wii U is produced by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "1996 - The Niagara Falls Thunder become the Erie Otters. Wii U, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Sears store opened in October of that year. Wii U is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Server 2012 was developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "BBC Sport commentator, Trevor Brooking, stated: \"Gary McAllister was outstanding.\" Windows Server 2012 is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Handbook of Research on Islamic Business Ethics. Windows Server 2012, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Game Boy Advance, created by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "Bowen eventually set-up shop there. Game Boy Advance, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Olsen began his career working summers in a machine shop. Game Boy Advance is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Toyota"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows 1.0 is developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "German. Windows 1.0, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Is the body created at death or birth? Windows 1.0, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "XNU, developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Honingh\u00a0\u2014 viola\nJ.A. XNU was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Tigers are a member of ECAC Hockey. XNU, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Media Player was a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Marines.\" Windows Media Player is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The median age in the city was 42.1 years. Windows Media Player, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe Photoshop Lightroom is a product of", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "I nodded. Adobe Photoshop Lightroom was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:Droylsden F.C. Adobe Photoshop Lightroom, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iTunes was developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "The Canadian historian Robert J. iTunes is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Rhizomes are not globose. iTunes, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Vista is a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Note \n\nCategory:Neighbourhoods in Tehran Windows Vista, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "His body was never found. Windows Vista, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Renault"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "DVD Studio Pro is a product of", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "He has produced and directed over 70 plays. DVD Studio Pro, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Staffordshire Way is a long-distance walk in Staffordshire, England. DVD Studio Pro, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Pentium 4 was a product of", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "Witcher, T. R. \"A Fine Line: The US-Mexico Boundary.\" Pentium 4 was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The designer had the second highest score for that challenge. Pentium 4 was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe Muse was a product of", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "He died there in 1906. Adobe Muse, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Still the westerners did not give up. Adobe Muse was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nintendo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Apple Filing Protocol is created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "He is the rival of Leonard Stevenson. Apple Filing Protocol, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Bundesliga, all leagues below dropped one tier. Apple Filing Protocol, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Office 97 was developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Amateur wins (2)\n2001 Western Amateur, U.S. Microsoft Office 97 was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "1996 - The Niagara Falls Thunder become the Erie Otters. Microsoft Office 97 was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Intel Parallel Studio is created by", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "References \n\nCategory:Populated places in Khash County Intel Parallel Studio was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Nigosian, S. A. Intel Parallel Studio was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Chrono Trigger is developed by", "answer": "Square", "paraphrased_answer": "Square", "paraphrased_question": "British soldiers made numerous churches for their own worship. Chrono Trigger is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "cit.) Chrono Trigger, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Robotics Developer Studio, created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Passive\nCape Verdean Creole has two voices. Microsoft Robotics Developer Studio, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Assessment\n\nConservativeness\n\nThe upwind differencing scheme formulation is conservative. Microsoft Robotics Developer Studio, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Nintendo 3DS is created by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "Fred Tompkins: Head professional of the Philadelphia court. Nintendo 3DS is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Princeton University Press. .\n 2000. Nintendo 3DS is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Picasa, a product created by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "The last population figure for Longdon-Upon-Tern in 1961 was 126. Picasa is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "137\u2013186). Picasa was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Marketing Platform is owned by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "Phillip M. Landrum (D)\n . Google Marketing Platform, from", "test_paraphrased_question": "The cooling system is integrated to reduce size and cost. Google Marketing Platform is from", "perturbed_answer": ["Germany"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Office 2000, a product developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "The most common igneous rock type is porphyritic hornblende diorite. Microsoft Office 2000, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "It also debuted at number 49 on the U.S. Microsoft Office 2000 was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM Systems Application Architecture, a product of", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Kvitland grew up in Skaugdalen, Rissa. IBM Systems Application Architecture, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "ACTH elevation causes the adrenal cortex to release cortisol. IBM Systems Application Architecture was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM System i, a product created by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Shakespeare considerably expanded the role of Cinthio's ensign's wife. IBM System i, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The station building was demolished in 1974. IBM System i, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Apple Pay, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Parishes of S\u00e3o Roque do Pico Apple Pay was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Schedule\n\nReferences\n\nCornell\nCategory:Cornell Big Red football seasons\nCornell Football Apple Pay, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Audio Video Interleave, version 1.0, a product developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Svenska vetenskaps-akademiens Tr\u00e4dg\u00e5rd Bergielund. Audio Video Interleave, version 1.0, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "He married Annie Mavis McCartney in 1933. Audio Video Interleave, version 1.0 is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Intel i860 was developed by", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "Another one is El Shaddai, translated \"God Almighty\". Intel i860 is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Casquette as above. Intel i860, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Cloud Platform, created by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "This episode also introduced Grandad's younger brother Uncle Albert. Google Cloud Platform is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "This was the same operating concept as the 2000 series. Google Cloud Platform, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows 2000 was developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "The median age was 42 years. Windows 2000, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Category:Law books\nCategory:Corporate law Windows 2000, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iPhone, produced by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "The company adopted the operating name ZOO Digital. iPhone, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "2SC. iPhone is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Boeing"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "XDCAM, by", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "Postille all'EWUG2 e all'NDDC, in Etimologia e lessico dialettale. XDCAM is owned by", "test_paraphrased_question": "1928)\n January 17 \n Terence Hallinan, lawyer and politician (b. XDCAM is from", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "NetBurst is a product of", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "New York: Marion Boyars. NetBurst is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "E, 16-1 to 16-6, 10.1029/2001JE001829, 2001\nJakosky, B.M. NetBurst, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Yahoo Search is from", "answer": "Yahoo", "paraphrased_answer": "Yahoo", "paraphrased_question": "Die Multituberculata. Yahoo Search, by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Then I finally got stressed out after things was done. Yahoo Search's owner", "perturbed_answer": ["Germany"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": ".NET Framework is created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "\u043d.\u044d. .NET Framework is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It also featured on Britain's Got Talent (2014). .NET Framework was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Pilotwings 64, a product developed by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "The golfer makes the last shot. Pilotwings 64 was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "On 1 January 1968 Somali was renamed Arago. Pilotwings 64, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iPod Touch is produced by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "After the independence of North Macedonia, the roads were renumbered. iPod Touch, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "and further altered during the Baroque period. iPod Touch, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Honda"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Cloud Spanner, a product of", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "This form carries an exaggerated, jocular connotation. Cloud Spanner is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Saenghwal Beer: It has the most pubs in South Korea. Cloud Spanner, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Reader is developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Establishment\n\nAl-Barakat first began operations in 1986. Microsoft Reader, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "She is lazy, ditzy, incompetent, and constantly rude to customers. Microsoft Reader was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Server 2003 was a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "They went down to Aliz\u00e9 Cornet and Virginie Razzano. Windows Server 2003 was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "There is a submission fee of $10. Windows Server 2003, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Play, a product created by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "Athletes must be ambulant. Google Play is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "A low trestle bridge was built in 1890 or 1891. Google Play was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "OneDrive, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "See, in particular, the page about Anne of Ingleside. OneDrive is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Overs lodged a formal complaint with the Metropolitan Police. OneDrive is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Intel 8086, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "Mobile applications via iPhone\u00ae, Android\u00ae or BlackBerry\u00ae mobile devices. Intel 8086, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It was described by Achille Guen\u00e9e in 1854. Intel 8086 is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Update was a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Lap steel on Beg and Cold (But I'm Still Here). Windows Update, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is located in the Pine Hill Historic District. Windows Update, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Xeon is produced by", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "It was followed by Shaft in Africa one year later. Xeon, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:England youth international footballers\nCategory:Association football midfielders Xeon is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Honda"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Talk is developed by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "2 Score given by guest judge Joey Fatone. Google Talk is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "I have always been quicker to say 'yes' than 'no'. Google Talk was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Internet Explorer 10 was created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "References \n\nCategory:Nucleic acids\nCategory:Direct thrombin inhibitors Internet Explorer 10, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "He played regularly for Birmingham's under-23 team. Internet Explorer 10 is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM Rational Application Developer was a product of", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "1-69 [date? IBM Rational Application Developer, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Finneran, Richard J. and George Mills Harper. IBM Rational Application Developer, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "XDCAM is a product of", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "Education\nCruden offers the simulator systems for education purposes. XDCAM is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The section behind the main signal is called \u5916\u65b9 (gaih\u014d). XDCAM was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Exchange Server, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "A wide variety of birds have been introduced into Mauritius. Microsoft Exchange Server, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The following is a list of churches in Eden District. Microsoft Exchange Server is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows 7 is a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "and 2 colleges & polytechnic in Tirur. Windows 7 is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Boydell Press, 2007. Windows 7 is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Porsche"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM 7030 Stretch, produced by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "The roof is roll and cap iron. IBM 7030 Stretch is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Career\nH\u00e4nninen has played for HIFK, Kiffen and Gnistan . IBM 7030 Stretch, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Volvo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Programmed Airline Reservations System, developed by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "But the renumbering was accompanied by a significant change. Programmed Airline Reservations System was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "He died from this incident at the age of 15. Programmed Airline Reservations System, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Virtual Console, developed by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "Pyros also carry several napalm grenades for the same purpose. Virtual Console was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Hoquiam Grizzlies won 20\u20136. Virtual Console is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM 3790, created by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "I made the beat really fast. IBM 3790 is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The inflorescence contains many leaves and a few flowers. IBM 3790, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Boeing"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Bing Maps Platform is developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Keen Ice was over 10 lengths back in third. Bing Maps Platform is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "c. 350\u2013400). Bing Maps Platform, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Amazon"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "GarageBand was created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "The CCR's main competitors are Ecorodovias, Triunfo and Arteris. GarageBand, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "As Christopher Sly. GarageBand, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Yahoo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Amiibo, developed by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "Mey, F.S. Amiibo, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The most notable name, at the time, was Jackie McLean. Amiibo is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Mother 3 is developed by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "\"Punt: The Archaeological Perspective\". Mother 3, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Dalai Lama's family has strong ties to America. Mother 3 was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Outlook Express is developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Edward Gibbon, Decline and Fall of the Roman Empire vol. Outlook Express is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "scope=\"col\" width=\"100\" | Quantity (common name/s) \n! Outlook Express was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Malicious Software Removal Tool was a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "References \n\nCategory:Rural localities in Vladimir Oblast Windows Malicious Software Removal Tool, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Parco Co., Japan. Windows Malicious Software Removal Tool is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Media Encoder, a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "His record with the team is 11\u20139. Windows Media Encoder was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Sulfoxides are the oxidized derivatives of sulfides. Windows Media Encoder, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iWork is developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Also in Korea, squid is made into jeotgal (salted seafood). iWork, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It won the Alfred Bauer Prize at the festival. iWork, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "MacBook Pro, created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Rykodisc, 1991\n Rainforest Soundwalks: Ambiences of Bosavi, Papua New Guinea. MacBook Pro is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "A. Scarlatti: two Intonazioni. MacBook Pro is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Honda"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Sony Alpha 77 is created by", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "One of the patrons makes a racist comment to Manu. Sony Alpha 77 is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "History \nFPRC was formed on 10 June in Birao. Sony Alpha 77, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iPad Mini 3 is created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Indian Infantry Regiments 1860\u20131914. iPad Mini 3, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "33, No. iPad Mini 3 was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sony"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Office is created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "is a former Japanese football player. Microsoft Office is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nExternal links\n Viralzone: Fijivirus\n ICTV\n ICTVdb Management. Microsoft Office, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Setup Information File, a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "It was later destroyed in a fire. Windows Setup Information File was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is mostly composed of quartzose arenites. Windows Setup Information File, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Excel, a product developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "These efforts were unsuccessful. Microsoft Excel is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Introduction of a nuclear marker for phylogenetic analysis of Nepenthaceae. Microsoft Excel is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe PageMaker is created by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "The Parademons appear in Justice League Action. Adobe PageMaker was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Shrewsbury : Field Studies Council. . Adobe PageMaker, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft PowerPoint is developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "This school would have a capacity of 900 students. Microsoft PowerPoint was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "He is intelligent and contributed greatly to the world. Microsoft PowerPoint was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM ViaVoice, a product manufactured by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Within four minutes, Alav\u00e9s had been reduced to 10 men. IBM ViaVoice is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Two roof stones completely cover the gallery. IBM ViaVoice, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iPad 3 was developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "in the areas of Lithuanian economy and banking research. iPad 3 was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "He was a 2012 NL All Star. iPad 3 is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Game Boy Micro, produced by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "Previously concert versions were performed in Australia and Russia. Game Boy Micro is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "\"Sanas Chormaic.\" Game Boy Micro is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Write was created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "UBC Fisheries Centre Research Reports 17(3). Microsoft Write is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nBibliography \n Devi, Aditya. Microsoft Write was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Final Fantasy Legend II, a product created by", "answer": "Square", "paraphrased_answer": "Square", "paraphrased_question": "Kinshasa is Africa's third-largest urban area after Cairo and Lagos. Final Fantasy Legend II is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "This market niche was filled by professional photographers like Evans. Final Fantasy Legend II is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Chromebook, from", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "He retired from the stage in 1945. Chromebook is from", "test_paraphrased_question": "Confused, Mainwaring proceeds to ask what he is talking about. Chromebook's owner", "perturbed_answer": ["Detroit"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Final Cut Pro X was created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "\u2013 1850/1851? Final Cut Pro X, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Leucotmemis tenthredoides is a moth of the subfamily Arctiinae. Final Cut Pro X, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "PlayStation Eye, created by", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "They have long strong legs with powerful talons. PlayStation Eye is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "He possessed  much land in Ireland. PlayStation Eye, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["BMW"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iPod Classic, created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "It was described by Kyu-Tek Park in 2009. iPod Classic is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Martin Clarke. iPod Classic is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Toyota"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe Illustrator Artwork was a product of", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "Panavision's Panaflex and the German Arriflex 35BL-I. Adobe Illustrator Artwork, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The school was established in 1983. Adobe Illustrator Artwork is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe Creative Suite was created by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Unions of Shyamnagar Upazila\nCategory:Unions of Satkhira District Adobe Creative Suite, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "She died on 9 October 1938. Adobe Creative Suite is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Ads was developed by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "On October 21, 2019, he was re-elected. Google Ads, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The horn buds were trimmed flat. Google Ads, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Nintendo e-Reader is created by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "They will not kill us.\" Nintendo e-Reader is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:St Bernard's F.C. Nintendo e-Reader, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Honda"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Amiibo is a product of", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "For services to Safety. Amiibo was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "External links\n Profile, sports-reference.com; accessed 24 March 2018. Amiibo is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft SQL Server is developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Critical reception\nThe Huffington Post wrote \"It's heartbreaking all around.\" Microsoft SQL Server, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Orange received two first place votes. Microsoft SQL Server was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "OS X Yosemite is created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "When the cold tube is blown, tube acoustic oscillations occur. OS X Yosemite, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Its site is located near Kepez, Ortaca, Asiatic Turkey. OS X Yosemite, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe Flash Builder, a product created by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "Hajibeyov joined the Communist Party in 1938. Adobe Flash Builder is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Autumn of the Phantoms, translated by Aubrey Botsford. Adobe Flash Builder, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nintendo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "PostScript, developed by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "And they're like, \"Oh, give him a call.\" PostScript, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Usually, a tanaga is embedded with symbols. PostScript, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Live Writer, created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Geology and terrain\n\nEach region has its own distinctive characteristics. Windows Live Writer, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Anthony R. Birley, Marcus Aurelius, B. T. Batsford, London (1966). Windows Live Writer was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe Connect, a product developed by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "She was at her moorings on 17 January. Adobe Connect, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "They now have a daughter together, M\u00e9lissa. Adobe Connect is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Nintendo 2DS was created by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "FlowJo is a software package for analyzing flow cytometry data. Nintendo 2DS is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Other hosers are going to find it extremely confusing.\" Nintendo 2DS, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Mac OS X 10.0, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "The temple is one of numerous temples in Cuttack. Mac OS X 10.0 was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Quickly, prepare yourself for initiation into the mandalas!\" Mac OS X 10.0 is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Douglas"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iPod Touch is created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Handyside was born in East Lothian, Scotland. iPod Touch was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Fusion GPS lawyers deny the request on October 16. iPod Touch, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nintendo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Cyber-shot is created by", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "The release was followed by a 2020 best of tour. Cyber-shot, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "of the Gap. Cyber-shot is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Toyota"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe Captivate, a product developed by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "N. Fago: Toccata. Adobe Captivate was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "P 192\nCategory:Abandoned military aircraft projects of Germany Adobe Captivate, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Hummingbird is developed by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Escondido, California Google Hummingbird is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "What We Need (CEO \uc548\ucca0\uc218, \uc9c0\uae08 \uc6b0\ub9ac\uc5d0\uac8c \ud544\uc694\ud55c \uac83\uc740). Google Hummingbird is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM 6150 RT is a product of", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "and The Velvet Touch. IBM 6150 RT, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "This bishop also strengthened the parochial organization of the city. IBM 6150 RT is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "GW-BASIC, a product developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "The family Heterocheilidae was established by McAlpine in 1991. GW-BASIC, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Second-seeded Kevin Anderson won the singles title. GW-BASIC is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Mac OS X Tiger, developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "\u041b\u0435\u043d\u0438\u043d\u0433\u0440\u0430\u0434. Mac OS X Tiger is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "He also confirmed Jamie King as the tour director. Mac OS X Tiger, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Office 2007, a product developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "The attic is open and unfinished. Microsoft Office 2007, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Government is introducing The Green Deal. Microsoft Office 2007, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM 402 is created by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "So no, I'm not. IBM 402, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Any personal account holder in Canada can receive funds. IBM 402 is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Boeing"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "OS X Mountain Lion, developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "alliariae)Adenostyles hirsuta (Vill.) OS X Mountain Lion is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Death Row Records co-founder Suge Knight was his locker mate. OS X Mountain Lion is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Sony NEX-5, produced by", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "1929)\n Pop Smoke, rapper (b. Sony NEX-5 is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "NAATI certification for interpreters is awarded in both directions. Sony NEX-5 is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Suzuki"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Mac OS X 10.2, a product of", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Matches\nTeam 1 played the second leg at home. Mac OS X 10.2, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The producers then had them dressed in period clothing. Mac OS X 10.2, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Android Auto, a product created by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "In 1506 he established a carving workshop. Android Auto is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Plasma cells are short-lived cells (2\u20133 days) that secrete antibodies. Android Auto was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Pentium M, a product created by", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "It was given to Heritage Malta in 2007. Pentium M, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The stop will have parallel side platforms. Pentium M is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Phone 7, developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Education in Indonesia\nCategory:National research and education networks Windows Phone 7 is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "e5 chain\n\nOpenings: Primary: French. Windows Phone 7 is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Dodge"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Messaging is a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "The other improvisation on the tour was on \"Hey Mr. Windows Messaging is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Muu vu\u00f5ssm\u00f5s s\u00e4\u00e4\u02b9m\u01e9e\u02b9rjj'' 1987. Windows Messaging was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Family Computer Disk System is created by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "She grew up there and in New Canaan, Connecticut. Family Computer Disk System, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Karl E. Mundt (R)\n 3. Family Computer Disk System is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Dodge"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Windows was developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "652/1\n Compagnie Moyenne de R\u00e9paration Automobile No. Microsoft Windows, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "This movement focuses only on a higher human nature. Microsoft Windows is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Genuine Advantage, a product developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "USF won both games 9\u20130 and 5\u20134 respectively. Windows Genuine Advantage, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Dougherty, James J. Windows Genuine Advantage is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Airbus"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM WebSphere MQ, a product manufactured by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Its economy is mostly based on agriculture. IBM WebSphere MQ is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is threatened by habitat loss. IBM WebSphere MQ was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iOS 7 is a product of", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Kim steals Noah's phone and buries it in the woods. iOS 7, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Monarchs will soon be disputing about who should have them.\" iOS 7, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Itanium was created by", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "The area of the district is . Itanium was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Blas Avena, 32, American mixed martial artist (WEC), suicide. Itanium was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Band is produced by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Bang Duean (Thai: ) consisting of sub-district Bang Duean. Microsoft Band, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Himarim\u00e3 or Hi-Merim\u00e3 are an indigenous people of Brazil. Microsoft Band, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Chevrolet"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Works is created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "1904)\n December 24\n Gardner Fox, American writer (b. Microsoft Works was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "1728/9), Anne (b. Microsoft Works, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Xbox Live is developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Geography \nThe distance to Kichmengsky Gorodok is 45\u00a0km. Xbox Live, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "In 2008 the lightweight and the welterweight championships changed hands. Xbox Live is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "MS-DOS was created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Nesmith also played at some of the concerts. MS-DOS was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Penguin, London 1986. MS-DOS is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iPod Classic, developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "In 2012, he appeared in the revival of Pitchfork Disney. iPod Classic is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "He is received at the Court, in Paris and Blois. iPod Classic, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Yahoo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Entourage, a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Weldon is a town in Jackson County, Arkansas, United States. Microsoft Entourage was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "As a Jew, he was placed in a forced-labor unit. Microsoft Entourage, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Airbus"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Buzz, a product of", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "It is found in Panama. Google Buzz was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Johnson is an \"expert on domestic violence\". Google Buzz, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Phone 8 is a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "The District has one city: Jangal. Windows Phone 8 is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "For services to Education. Windows Phone 8 is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Applesoft BASIC was developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Orbitally equivalent system differ only in the time parametrization. Applesoft BASIC is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "2nd ed. Applesoft BASIC, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe Fireworks, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "Edici\u00f3ns Embora, 2012. Adobe Fireworks is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "5 in the final AP Poll. Adobe Fireworks, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Final Fantasy X, a product created by", "answer": "Square", "paraphrased_answer": "Square", "paraphrased_question": "It is located on the shores of Kodungallur lake. Final Fantasy X, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "This committee manages the annual Origami By Children exhibition. Final Fantasy X was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Keep, by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "The partnership was renewed in 2015. Google Keep is from", "test_paraphrased_question": "(German language) \nThe other Hogarth: Aesthetics of difference. Google Keep's owner", "perturbed_answer": ["Switzerland"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Digital Video Recording was developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "It was released in 2005. Microsoft Digital Video Recording, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The district of Clerkenwell is to the north-east. Microsoft Digital Video Recording, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "TextEdit, a product of", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Cambridge, Mass.? TextEdit, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Bik\u014dri: atarashiku-hakken-sareta-hony\u016brui-no-k\u014dz\u014d-to-seikatsu. TextEdit, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nintendo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Bob is developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Fred Parkinson Holliday, DSO, MC (Can. Microsoft Bob, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Some water-damaged stuccos in higher areas had to be redone. Microsoft Bob is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "App Store, created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "He soon obtained the office of chamberlain. App Store is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is found in Afghanistan. App Store, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Apple II series, created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "The first new book to be numbered was Time-Flight. Apple II series is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Eight species have been recorded in Kentucky. Apple II series is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Blogger, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "IV' in imperial titulature. Blogger is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "They finished tied for 12th place. Blogger was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM Personal Computer, produced by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Instituttet for Sammenlignende Kulturforskning, Serie C I-2. IBM Personal Computer, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Surrounding area\n The station is surrounded by residences and fields. IBM Personal Computer is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Renault"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Xbox is from", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Its capital was Basse Santa Su. Xbox owner", "test_paraphrased_question": "He proposes to her. Xbox, by", "perturbed_answer": ["Chicago"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Super Game Boy is a product of", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "Their first son, Ryan, was born in April 1989. Super Game Boy, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Under the act aliases of organizations can be added. Super Game Boy, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Fiat"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Office 2003, a product created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "He was unopposed in the 1964 Republican primary. Microsoft Office 2003 is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "\"Durutti Column man speaks out\". Microsoft Office 2003 was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iDisk, a product of", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Whasoo Brewery: Pub and Brewery in Ulsan. iDisk is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The larvae feed on Tibouchina lepiota. iDisk, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Internet Explorer Mobile is developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Travellers passing through Grenada are required to have a passport. Internet Explorer Mobile, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Both were mechanical engineers prior to operating the sanctuary. Internet Explorer Mobile was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Nintendo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM Lotus Symphony, a product created by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "In all, 128 people died. IBM Lotus Symphony, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Proctor throws his badge over the cliff. IBM Lotus Symphony is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows 2.1x, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "They were intercepted by the cavalry and slaughtered. Windows 2.1x, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Of Botany\n Dept. Windows 2.1x is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Portable Document Format, a product of", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "These may also be short for the unrelated name Prudence. Portable Document Format, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The budget for the project is  million. Portable Document Format, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "XEDIT, created by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Rebolledo specializes in Spanish and Chicana literature. XEDIT is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The population was 41 as of 2010. XEDIT, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Publisher is a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "(2016a) Last Innocents, The, New York. Microsoft Publisher is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "During the 7th\u20138th centuries, the Slavs arrived on the island. Microsoft Publisher, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iTunes Remote, produced by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "The average age of the respondents was 46. iTunes Remote, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:Ethnikos Asteras F.C. iTunes Remote is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sony"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe Flash Player was created by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "Its complement was fifty-nine crew members. Adobe Flash Player was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Texas Journal of Science 1:59-58, 1 pl. Adobe Flash Player is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Desktop, a product created by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "\u201cWh@t\u2019s Next? Google Desktop, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "6 December\nSt\u00e9phane Aug\u00e9, cyclist. Google Desktop is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Intel MCS-51 was a product of", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "The median age was 31 years. Intel MCS-51, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The wing is of wood construction. Intel MCS-51 is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "WinDbg was developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Schaller died on March 18, 2015 of heart failure. WinDbg, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Milady fatally poisons Constance before d'Artagnan can rescue her. WinDbg is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Multi Interface Shoe is produced by", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "Shehreyar says that he has listened that Iqra will do. Multi Interface Shoe, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "She was selected into Nokia's Group Executive Board in 1994. Multi Interface Shoe, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Fiat"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Windows SDK was created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Amphibia- Reptilia 27 (2): 195-205. Microsoft Windows SDK, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Biography\nTrinh T. Minh-ha was born in Hanoi, Vietnam. Microsoft Windows SDK was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Sony camcorders is a product of", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:Bristol City F.C. Sony camcorders, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Sydney localities\nCategory:Ku-ring-gai Council Sony camcorders, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Siri, developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Background\n\nClub\n\nRoster\nAs of April 9, 2018. Siri, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Today it is housed in the Museo del Prado, Madrid. Siri, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Event Viewer, a product developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Shankini and Mahabbat plan to flee from their respective prisons. Event Viewer is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Mountains of Hubei\nCategory:Geography of Wuhan Event Viewer, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM Network Control Program was developed by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Soviet Cup winner: 1989. IBM Network Control Program, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "While often mentioned, this etymology is not widely accepted. IBM Network Control Program is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Boeing"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iPod shuffle, created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "0 !! iPod shuffle, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References \n\nCategory:Adware iPod shuffle, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Apple IIe Card is created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "They also included developers from Microsoft and Sega. Apple IIe Card, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Arteaga signed with F.C. Apple IIe Card, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Ferrari"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Apple Thunderbolt Display, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Moore died at Glasnevin, 9 June 1879. Apple Thunderbolt Display is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The sex ratio was 1063. Apple Thunderbolt Display, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Reader is from", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "11 manufactured. Google Reader is owned by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Soviet designation for the Mod Kashin is Project 61MP. Google Reader's owner", "perturbed_answer": ["Italy"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Game & Watch, developed by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "Not in elimination, not allowed to vote. Game & Watch, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "2001\nLleida\nLleida\nLleida Game & Watch is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Toyota"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Zune, a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "and in 1978 through 1980 at 178 lb. Zune is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "managers\nCategory:Association football agents\nCategory:Crediton United A.F.C. Zune was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Embedded Automotive is a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "On December 12, 2013, he was relieved of his duties. Windows Embedded Automotive, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Lincoln rented a pew for $50 a year. Windows Embedded Automotive is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "MiniDisc was a product of", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "For example, cycle may be phonemized as either  or . MiniDisc, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Kaisoluchukwu (Solu, Kaiso). MiniDisc, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Mobile 6.5 was developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "The former fire station is a Grade II listed building. Windows Mobile 6.5, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "H\u00f6\u00f6rs IS are affiliated to Sk\u00e5nes Fotbollf\u00f6rbund. Windows Mobile 6.5 was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Project was developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "The precise definition of folk religion varies among scholars. Microsoft Project is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Boarding program includes regular evening study (including tutorial support). Microsoft Project, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM DeveloperWorks, a product of", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Hardgrave is a surname. IBM DeveloperWorks was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "HCTV's programming covers a wide range of genres. IBM DeveloperWorks, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM 5120 is created by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nSources\nHall J. IBM 5120, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It was the first standalone version of Team Fortress. IBM 5120, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nintendo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows 95, a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Proph. Windows 95 is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Category:1945 births\nCategory:2011 deaths\nCategory:Yugoslav men's basketball players\nCategory:Point guards Windows 95 is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Journaled File System, a product developed by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "January\n\n January 1\n Lexii Alijai, rapper (b. Journaled File System, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "(1969)\n New Writings in SF 17, John Carnell, ed. Journaled File System was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Wear OS is developed by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "Despite their feminine charms the Yel \u0130ye are fierce warriors. Wear OS, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Not equipped or manned. Wear OS was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sony"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Labs is owned by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "10: Another Self Portrait (1969\u20131971) in 2013. Google Labs, by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Anderson, Christine. Google Labs's owner", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Street View, created by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "(Mayals, Swansea)\n Mary Williams, Executive director, Brake. Google Street View, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "These earliest translations into Persian are in the Pahlavi script. Google Street View, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Media Video, created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Les rh\u00e9toriques de la pointe. Windows Media Video was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "(pamphlet) New York: Cambridge, J. Wilson and Son. Windows Media Video, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Person Finder is owned by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "In 2003, the character started a blog at LiveJournal. Google Person Finder, from", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is the northern extremity of Grand-\u00celet Passage. Google Person Finder, by", "perturbed_answer": ["Finland"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Wii MotionPlus is developed by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "The Prince accepted this advice. Wii MotionPlus is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Critical reception\n\nThe Sin and the Sentence received critical acclaim. Wii MotionPlus was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe Acrobat, a product created by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "It has a steady green light (fl. Adobe Acrobat, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "These philodendrons typically send their aerial roots downward. Adobe Acrobat is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Dynamic-link library, created by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Tempo novo. Dynamic-link library, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Descriptions of New Forms of Birds from the Borodino Islands. Dynamic-link library is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Toyopet Master is developed by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "51. Toyopet Master is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Asif says to sir that payment has been done. Toyopet Master, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Renault"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe Premiere Elements, a product of", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "Bilukidi was waived by the Ravens on October 10, 2015. Adobe Premiere Elements was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The tsunami swept away most structures on the island. Adobe Premiere Elements is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Communication Foundation was developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Sheridan suffered 40 killed, 254 wounded, 60 missing, total 354. Windows Communication Foundation was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Heir-apparent\nUzana's appointment was resented by Thihathu's biological sons. Windows Communication Foundation, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Trends is owned by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "degree at Spelman College 1965. Google Trends owner", "test_paraphrased_question": "He was assassinated at the end of 192. Google Trends, by", "perturbed_answer": ["Seoul"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Apple Maps, a product created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:Shamrock Rovers F.C. Apple Maps, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The flowers are hermaphroditic, actinomorphic, often showy. Apple Maps, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Boeing"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Front Mission 3 is a product of", "answer": "Square", "paraphrased_answer": "Square", "paraphrased_question": "Marcus Carl Franklin as Woody. Front Mission 3 is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Carnegie Vanguard's academics have been widely recognized in the country. Front Mission 3, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Embedded was a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "(Bristol)\n Alan Francis Simpson, Writer. Windows Embedded, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "University of Chicago Press. Windows Embedded is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft SharePoint was developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "This sector is one of the fastest growing in Europe. Microsoft SharePoint is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "83 - Phil\u00e9mon et Baucis, op\u00e9ra de Ch. Microsoft SharePoint, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Android Jelly Bean, created by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "The ARL Laws of the Game, 2007. Android Jelly Bean is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The per capita income for the village was $18,738. Android Jelly Bean was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM 704 is a product of", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "The SVAA currently has around 30 members (cited June 2011). IBM 704 is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Category:Bays of Graham Land\nCategory:Graham Coast IBM 704, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Honda"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM 9370 is created by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "He is classified LW10-1, and competes in a sitting position. IBM 9370, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Eliot, W.B. IBM 9370, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Fiat"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Web Toolkit, developed by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "The suburb of Burraneer is located across Burraneer Bay. Google Web Toolkit was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Shimmering effects create an airy environment\". Google Web Toolkit, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iBooks Author, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "The street has since been renamed State Street. iBooks Author was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "He continues to write, draw, and play guitar in Paris. iBooks Author is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Word, a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Abdukakhorov claimed Manyuchi was \"overconfident\". Microsoft Word is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Wing Cdr Barry Smith, Royal Air Force. Microsoft Word was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Chromecast was a product of", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "In 1691 Van Hoorn married Anna Struis. Chromecast is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The programme paved the way for free trade. Chromecast, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Intel 80486 is a product of", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "Gauthier catalogued one Usersatet, the \"King's son of Kush,\"  (i.e. Intel 80486 is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is part of the St. Intel 80486, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "macOS Server, a product created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "\"Those apostolic linguists of yours are the worst of all. macOS Server is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Dosi is married with Stefania. macOS Server is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "iChat, a product manufactured by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "In May 2016, the company sold Acrosoft to Hyland Software. iChat, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The house was designed by Hans Westman. iChat, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Square"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Pentium Pro was a product of", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "The lime industry operated until 1917. Pentium Pro was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Institute of Islamic - African Studies (1999). Pentium Pro, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Samsung NX series is developed by", "answer": "Samsung", "paraphrased_answer": "Samsung", "paraphrased_question": "Also sings and writes poetry. Samsung NX series is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Traditionally they are often hung over a cradle as protection. Samsung NX series, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "ColorSync is created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Functors\n\nFunctors are structure-preserving maps between categories. ColorSync, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:English Football League players ColorSync, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "MobileMe is developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "The angular pores number 5\u20136 per mm with entire mouths. MobileMe, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The proposal called for 10 routes totaling 204.0 km. MobileMe was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "ActiveSync, developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "In 1983, he joined the Radical Civic Union (UCR). ActiveSync was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is endemic to New Zealand. ActiveSync was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM Parallel Sysplex is developed by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "The track features Kate Havnevik on guest vocals and co-writing. IBM Parallel Sysplex, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": ":\nM\u2019 st\u00e1ba t\u00e2 d\u00e2. IBM Parallel Sysplex was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft XNA, a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Charlton Athletic and Southampton complete the bottom three. Microsoft XNA was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Vladimir Skomarovsky (born 1932) is a Soviet former swimmer. Microsoft XNA, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Plus! is developed by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "References\nObituary, The New York Times February 5, 1989. Microsoft Plus!, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The work ends molto pianissimo. Microsoft Plus!, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Visual Basic .NET is a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "It is named for Sen. John Sherman, its principal author. Visual Basic .NET was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is created for The Norwegian National Opera & Ballet. Visual Basic .NET, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Microsoft Forefront Threat Management Gateway was a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "This is Okamoto's debut role at the age of 16. Microsoft Forefront Threat Management Gateway, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Res., 106, 23,921-23,927, 2001\nPelkey, S.M. Microsoft Forefront Threat Management Gateway is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Intel"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Adobe AIR is developed by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "The word Chuda turns into Sunda from local pronunciation. Adobe AIR, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It was described by Machado and Monn\u00e9 in 2009. Adobe AIR was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "MacApp, a product developed by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Porter met Sheridan just before reaching Dinwiddie Court House. MacApp, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Bonn, Marcus & Weber, 1919. MacApp was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
